<Help>
  <!-- Help dialog's title -->
  <title>Notification Center Help</title>
  <!-- A help entry -->
  <helpEntry>
     <!-- Help entry heading, bold font -->
     <header>
        The Notification Center Table allows a user to view and delete data delivery notifications.
     </header>
     <!-- Help entry text, normal font.  Line breaks in text are passed through to display -->
     <text />
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        File Menu
     </header>
     <text />
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Set as Default
     </header>
     <text>
Set the current configuration settings to be the default settings for the table. When the table is opened the saved default settings are applied.
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Load Configuration...
     </header>
     <text>
Load a previously saved configuration file. Select from the Available Configuration Files list and click the Load button to load a configuration file. Use the Preview button to view the XML 
        associated with the configuration file.
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Save Configuration
     </header>
     <text>
Save the current configuration settings to the most recently saved file name. The first time Save Configuration is accessed, select to save either at the User or Site level and enter a file name. Click the Save button to save the file. Use the Load Configuration menu item to load a saved configuration.
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Save Configuration As...
     </header>
     <text>
Save the current configuration settings to a named file that may be loaded in the future. In the Save Configuration dialog select to save either at the User or Site level and enter a file name. Click the Save button to save the file. Use the Load Configuration menu item to load a saved configuration.
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Delete Configuration...
     </header>
     <text>
Delete a saved configuration file.
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Exit
     </header>
     <text>
Close the Notification Center.
    </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Edit Menu
     </header>
     <text />
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Find...
     </header>
     <text>
Find and highlight items in the table using the Find dialog. The Case Sensitive option allows a user to search text that is capitalization sensitive. The Exclude option allows a user to search the table for items that exclude the entered text. The Case Sensitive and Exclude options may be used in conjunction with another. The Column Selection grouping allows users to search a specific column in the table. After the search criteria has been selected, click the Find Next button to perform the search. The Highlight All button highlights all the rows matching the find criteria. Close the Find dialog using the Close button.
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Delete by Priority
     </header>
     <text>
Delete all rows in the table having a specific priority. (Note: Notifications only deleted from the user view and not permanently deleted from the database.)    
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Delete Older Than Selected
     </header>
     <text>
Delete all rows in the table having a date in the Time column that is older than the currently highlighted row. (Note: Notifications only deleted from the user view and not permanently deleted from the database.)
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Delete Notifications
     </header>
     <text>
Delete the currently highlighted row(s) in the table. (Note: Notifications only deleted from the user view and not permanently deleted from the database.)
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Settings Menu
     </header>
     <text />
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Configure Table...
     </header>
     <text>
The Initial Startup Configuration items are set when the table is opened.  Check the Load All Messages check box to display all messages in the table that are contained in the database. Enter a number of messages or hours amount in the Load Last spinner to select the amount of messages or number of hours of messages to display in the table. Set the Initial Sort Column and either Sort Ascending or Sort Descending to sort the table by a specific column upon opening.
        
The Display Configuration items refresh the table upon clicking OK. Select the number of Rows Per Page using the selection drop down. Select the image setting for the Priority table column using the radio buttons. Select to make columns hidden or visible using the arrows provided. After making selections, click the OK button to configure the table. (Note: Unless the configuration is set to the default or saved, changes will be lost when the table is closed.)
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
  <helpEntry>
     <header>
        Filter Table...
     </header>
     <text>
A user may filter the table by user, by subscription or by priority.  In the Filter by User section, the list of available user names are in the Available Users column. If users are moved to the Selected Users list, the corresponding columns containing those user names will be displayed in the Notification Table. Use the arrows to move users back and forth from the Available Users list to the Selected Users list. (Note: User names are not duplicated and appear only once either in the Available or Selected lists.) The Always include my notifications check box may be used to keep the currently logged in user in the Selected Users column. 

In the Filter by Subscription section, the list of available subscription names are in the Available Subscriptions column. If subscriptions are moved to the Selected Subscriptions list the corresponding columns containing those subscription names will be displayed in the Notification Table. Use the arrows to move subscriptions back and forth from the Available Subscriptions list to the Selected Subscriptions list. (Note: Subscription names are not duplicated and appear only once either in the Available or Selected lists.) 

In the Filter by Priority section, select which columns containing specific priorities to display using the checkboxes.
     </text>
  </helpEntry>
</Help>
